A Guide to the Papers of Ernest Hemingway, 1925-1961, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Dotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 March 31, LS, 4 pp. on 4 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 3:99)
    Thanks for advice, help, etc. Can't give a reading on television situation as is pooped having written Life explaining delay on Mano-a-Mano. Up to 63,562 words, and offering to return advance or re-negotiate. Wrote Scribner's to scratch Paris book from fall list due to overextension of time put in on Mano-a-Mano. Discussion of business matters regarding books and stage productions. Refers to The Gambler, Nun, and Radio, which took place in a hospital in Billings, Montana. Glad Hotchner sold Killers to German television. Letter in the hand of Hemingway's secretary. 6250-f
  - Mr. Papa [Ernest Hemingway] to "Bron" [Bronislaw Zielinski], 1960 April 16, LS, 2 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 3:100)
    Hopes Zielinski has been receiving his letters. Seems that Zielinski did not receive two of his last letters. Feels uneasy about postal communications. Hemingway would never break off a correspondence even though he is a poor correspondent and is working very hard that his friends get "nothing in proportion to his daily work." Let him know when he receives this letter. Letter in the hand of Hemingway's secretary. 6250-g
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 May 9, LS, 3 pp. on 3 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 3:101)
    Thanks for T.V. Guide reviews. Alfred [Rice] so depressing it looks as if he is working for other people. "Coop" [Gary Cooper] is in hospital and going to Naples on a picture. How do the various projects stand? Word count over 92,000. That is much too many. Will finish 20th of this month. Mary's arm progressing well. Discusses his writing. Letter in the hand of Hemingway's secretary. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 July 5, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:1)
    Enclosed $500 check [not present] for apartment expenses and cost of typing and copying bullfight manuscript. Hope his back is fine now. Hemingway feels bad about the "Schoonmaker business." 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 August 7, ALS, 2 pp. on 2 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Sending cable to protect from libel. Found out Luis Miguel [DominguÍn] going "hog wild" in Spain on anything to do with horses being sleaved [sic]. The fact everybody knows they are sleaved [sic] means nothing. Legally you would have to prove it and the government won't investigate the ring. Doesn't want to risk Life with any libel suit. Lots of bad stuff going on. Antonio [Ordez] dealing with plenty sordid stuff: "whole set-up bad." Horn cutting worse than ever, but they crack down when Antonio's bulls are involved. Hemingway doesn't feel too good. 6250-f
  - Pedro Ro Papa [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 September 8, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:3)
    Sending check. [Belly] in really lousy shape. Make sure Alfed [Rice] pays him. Hopes to clean up work for book. Never was so dead in the head in his life. Starting to pull out of it. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 September 17, 4 pp. on 2 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:4)
    Returned to Madrid for four days rest. Discusses Antonio [Ordez] and bullfights. Asks why Hotchner never cashed the $5000 check. Life crossed them up; had arguments over the pictures of bullfights. Hemingway "the laughing stock of anyone who knows anything about bull fighting and has seen piece and regarded as the crook and double crosser of all Time." Numerous problems with pictures of bull fighting: "Would rather be smashed up like in Africa any number of times than have the feeling that page of pictures gave me." Hemingway has to try not to think that he is destroyed as an honest guy. Made both a fool and a double crosser after all his care to be true. For what sum would they let him not publish Spanish edition? 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to [Edward] Hotchner, 1960 September 18, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:5)
    Telegram. That many stories is a book. Would ask for seven, not ninety under 5. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to [Edward] Hotchner, 1960 September 19, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:6)
    Telegram. Hotchner should ask for book length price of $100,000, reducing as necessary. Studios value according to the price they pay. Ten stories of his should be expensive package. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to [Edward] Hotchner, 1960 September 22, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:7)
    Telegram. Still waiting. Call, cable when he receives this as he is held there until he hears from Hotchner. 6250-f
  - Logrono [Ernest Hemingway] to [Edward] Hotchner, 1960 September 24, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:8)
    Telegram. Will call Tuesday a.m. unless he cables Monday. Antonio [Ordez] greatest. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to [Edward] Hotchner, 1960 October 21, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:9)
    Telegram. Have information that Wald wants film badly. Inform any guests if arrived. No financial problems, no worries. Writing soon. Tried calling." 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1960 October 25, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:10)
    Enclosed is a $1500 check [not present] for Val's [Valerie Danby-Smith] tuition at the Dramatic Academy and living expenses. Hemingway doesn't want Val to arrive in New York with no backing. New York is expensive, not only to live but to eat properly. 6250-f
  - E.H. [Ernest Hemingway] to Val [Valerie Danby-Smith], 1960 October 25, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:11)
    Impossible for Hemingway to work unless he knows she is all right. Can write him in Sun Valley. He loves her very much and misses her help all the time. A rough fall and "the whole purpose of being here [Ketchum] to work is destroyed" unless he knows she is well. Wishes her luck and know that he loves her and wants everything good for her. 6250-f
  - Papa Mary [Ernest and Mary Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1961 January 10, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:12)
    Telegram. NWA on strike. Provides directions for Hotchner to get to them. Hemingway tells his weight. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1961 January 30, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:13)
    Talks about incoming mail. Weight down to 170 which is too low. Tells him when to call in order to discuss [Frank] Corsaro. Wire when contracts are done, and have Alfred [Rice] wire when deposits are made. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1961 February 18, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:14)
    Discusses his business talks with Alfred [Rice]. Business transactions. Hotchner had expenses as producer. Hemingway only supplied stories. He is working hard. 6250-f
  - Mr. Papa [Ernest Hemingway] to "Bron" [Bronislaw Zielinski], 1961 February 24, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:15)
    Hemingway shocked that Alfred [Rice] did not inform him of Zielinski's Pen Club prize for translation of Hemingway's works into Polish. Hemingway was very sick at the Mayo Hospital in Minnesota. Sends belated congratulations. Hemingway a bad correspondent because he has been very ill. 6250-g
  - Ernest Hemingway to Mr. A. E. Hotchner, 1961 March 2, TLS, 3 pp. on 3 l. (Box-folder 4:16)
    Hemingway documents the rights Hotchner has with all Hemingway's writings. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1961 March 4, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:17)
    Letter regarding agreement Alfred [Rice] sent to Hemingway. Sent copy to Hotchner to sign. 6250-f
  - "Papa" [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch-Muru" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1961 March 6, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:18)
    Tells Hotchner that letters are scarce, so everyone picks them up and reads them; if he has problems, etc. put them on separate sheet of paper for his eyes only. Working out present book, and has to go day to day on health business. Weight is bit low and wants to be sure on that end before taking on further work and movements. He doesn't want to worry Mary. 6250-f
  - Ernest Hemingway to [Merle] Armitage, n.d., ALS, 2 pp. on 1 p. with typed copy. (Box-folder 4:19)
    Thanks for letter. Happy he liked book. Answers his questions about Sidney Franklin and bullfighters. Latter at their best when bullfighting, and at their worst at a place such as United Artists lot with Sam Goldwyn. Likes "the old bugger" very much. Sees him on top of wave, and broke Also. If he sees him, ask him to write Hemingway what he thinks of his book [Death in the Afternoon?]. 6250-c
  - Ernest Hemingway to [Richard] Armstrong, "Friday,", ALS photocopy, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:20)
    Appreciates the trouble Armstrong has taking for them. Why not drop in and have a drink? Original tipped in The Sun Also Rises, PS 3515. E37 S8 1930 copy 3. 6250-t
  - Hemingstein [Ernest Hemingway] to Marlene Dietrich, n.d., AL draft, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:21)
    My Dearest Kraut. Thinks readings will be fine. Hopes London good. Hemingway going back to Finca. Refers to "page 488 on book." Draft of telegram. 6250-f
  - EH [Ernest Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], n.d., DS, 1 Christmas card. (Box-folder 4:22)
    Christmas greetings. 6250-f
  - "Papa" and "Mary" [Ernest and Mary Hemingway] to [Aaron Edward Hotchner], n.d., DS, 1 Christmas card (Box-folder 4:23)
    Hemingway proud of Hotchner. 6250-f
  - Ernest Hemingway to [Houghton Mifflin & Co.], n.d., ANS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:24)
    On the poetry of Archibald MacLeish. Indicates that he doesn't want to write about MacLeish as he is fond of him. Doesn't believe friends should write about each other's works. States that even those who do not like him or what he writes must see by now that he is a great poet. Autograph note by Archibald MacLeish in upper left hand corner: "Bob: This, of course, is written as an excerpt (in quotes) from a letter to H. M. Co. from E. H.. He sent it to me with apologies for not writing you direct as he is very busy. A." 6250-c
  - Ernest [Hemingway] to [Charles Scribner], n.d., ALS fragment, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:25)
    Received Dave Randall's letter and assures manuscript of The Green Hills of Africa is authentic. Jane Armstrong did a wonderful job copying it for Hemingway. She was very poor and broke so Hemingway gave her the manuscript because it would be "worth money some day." Please try to give her all you can for the manuscript. Original letter in autograph manuscript of The Green Hills of Africa. 6250-a
  - Ernest Hemingway to Mr. Vance, n.d., ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:26)
    Sends inscription to paste in one of his books. It's a bother to send a book back and forth. 6250-c
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "My Sweet Ed" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1949?] March 7, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:27)
    Mary asks if Hotchner "is a Papa yet?" Mentions Cosmopolitan treachery. Anne-Marie Cloche thrilled about ballet and plans to go to New York for its opening. Mary broke her leg skiing at Cortina and are delayed in returning to Paris. Sailing March 21. 6250-f
  - Mary Hemingway to "Honey Bun" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1951 May 29, TLS, 2 pp. on 2 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:28)
    Papa now finished war and chasing part of book and it's magnificent. So different from The Old Man and the Sea, which is a violin solo. With situation more complex and startling, frightening action. Just finished second annual marlin fishing tournament and thinks she could do a really good story about her experiences: ten hours a day for three days. On second day took 240 involuntary shower baths and caught one fish. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Honey Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1951 June 15, TLS, 2 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 4:29)
    Ladies Home Journal not interested in her story. Free to sell elsewhere. Discusses Brandt's interest and requirements of Post for story. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Honey Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1952] July 13, TLS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:30)
    Discusses her visit to parents and her boredom. They are going to publish The Old Man and the Sea story this fall. Convinced it is purest and best thing Ernest Hemingway has done. Won't offend Carl Brandt, will it? He was so efficient regarding marlin fishing job. Would Today's Woman let her know when they want story, how long, etc.? 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Honey Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1952] November 14, ALS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:31)
    Compliments him on a good story in Post. His year in Italy gets closer ever day. Life is good with them now. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Dearest Hotches" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1954] March 30, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:32)
    Just "the damndest, worst, dirtiest luck in the world, not even fit to happen to meanest SOBs." Hotchner falls sick and they couldn't operate him soon enough. Mary tells of her own medical problems that caused her inability to have a baby. Contented with practically everything, except McCarthy. P.S. Papa had a lot of internal breakage and a concussion and then another accident in a forest fire. We didn't tell the press. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1955?] June 21, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:33)
    Talks about Hotchner's planned trip to visit them. Hemingway's plan to go over July 2. Sending manuscript with Papa's additions. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Dearest Hotch-Puss" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1956] November 7, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:34)
    Regarding possible trip with them through English countryside. Papa's health O.K. now after stringent regime. Ava [Gardner?] came with script for The Sun Also Rises which was a mess. Papa is re-writing. Discusses political affairs in Hungary and Egypt, and is sorry that she is contributing nothing as a member of the human race. "Papa says, 'Never lose faith in the firm.'" 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Dearest Hotchpuss" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1956 December 28, TLS, 2 pp. on 2 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:35)
    Papa healthy again with his cholesterol down. Their plans to stay in their old room on the Ile. Hemingway is "bored shitless" following his health regime. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch Presh" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1957] April 4, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:36)
    Talks about her burgeoning garden. Medicos put Papa on even a stricter regime than in Paris. No hard liquor at all. He is managing "somehow to support the boredom which must accompany the being forever sober." Blood tests show definitive improvement. Mary asks Hotchner if he has read [Lael Tucker] Wertenbaker's Death of a Man and, if so, what he thought about it? Includes autograph note to Hotchner from Ernest Hemingway. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch darling" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1958 August 26, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:37)
    Explains reasons for not writing. Worries about book and hopes it will sell big to Hollywood and television. Hopes Hotchner can manage with 25% income tax for year. Papa started new thing and is working in single-minded devotion. He's in good shape with fine spirits except for massive irritation over Alfred's "boobiest blunder yet." Mary was able to accomplish one thing: getting new road almost saved from billboards. Originally enclosed with Ernest Hemingway to Hotchner, 1958 August 26. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch darling" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1958 November 5, TLS photocopy, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:38)
    "Four rollicking rambunctious weeks of Idaho brand revelry." Tells Hotchner all about their living conditions, the log cabin, shootable birds, deer, etc. Hunted every day. Papa is in great shape, masterminding the shooting. He works mornings and shoots evenings. Hemingway's work is going good. What is Hotchner waiting for? Come visit. Written on verso of Hemingway to Hotchner, 1958 November 5. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotchalito Caro" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], 1959 January 7, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:39)
    Snow for Christmas finished duck season, with Papa winding up with three doubles. The day before with three triples. New house is great. Discusses all the Christmas presents. New Year's Eve with Leonard Bernstein, her musical hero, "that all time, record-breaking jerk." He got more insufferable and he was close to having his phony face badly bruised. Heard about Cuba in New York Times and their house is in good shape except for a few blown out windows. Hopes they can get a year or two of decent living before they start mutilating and murdering each other again. Thanks for the gift of the cheese. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotchicante" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1959] September 6, APCS, 1 item. (Box-folder 4:40)
    Town cheerful and noisy as ever. Antonio [Ordez] has many corridas in September. Keep your fingers crossed. Included Antonio's dates in France. Postcard Also signed by Annie, [Ernest Hemingway?], Valerie, and Bill. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotchkisible" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1959] November 8, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:41)
    Regarding plans. Big party with Antonio [Ordez], etc. on Papa's Saint's Day. Will fly to Chicago to get place ready for Ernest Hemingway. He is driving to Idaho. Can't assess damage done to partnership last summer in Spain by Bill Davis. Doesn't know if it is reparable, but hopes so. Antonio and Carmen happy there. Papa to get to Ketchum November 15th or 16th. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch dear" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], [1961] May 4, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:42)
    Received long letter from Hemingway. More lucid that he's been for some time, harping on finances. He has to buy clothes. Wants to start working and be out of there as soon as he can. She wrote back that Hemingway should not get out until they are sure his cure is complete. Doesn't want repetition of the last three months. Can Hotchner talk to Dr. Cattell about this? She feels Hemingway may need thorough psychoanalysis. Not sure Dr. [Howard] Rome is man to do it, as he never went into depth regarding cause of Hemingway's hallucinations. Maybe transfer Hemingway to Menninger's. Hemingway would have to consent. Repetition of last three months would destroy her in one way or another. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Honey Hotch" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], n.y. July 4, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:43)
    Mary claims she is an "Indian giver," as she decided not to send her travel diaries to Hotchner on Hemingway's advice since Hotchner had a healthy memory anyway. Gives the itinerary of their trip. Once she has something he would like, she will send it immediately. 6250-f
  - Mary [Hemingway] to "Hotch cher" [Aaron Edward Hotchner], n.y. [1956?] December 13, ANS, 1 Christmas Card (Box-folder 4:44)
    Asks Hotchner to use this picture [not present] for the back jacket of his first book. Hemingway told Mary to relay that he finally "butchered them at Auteuil" at the horse races. They are there until January 23rd. 6250-f
  - Ralph MacA. Ingersoll to Joseph Losey, 1939 March 22, D, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:45)
    Telegram. Can't do it. Will discuss. 6250-a
  - [Ralph MacA. Ingersoll] to Joe [Losey], 1939 March 22, TL carbon copy, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:46)
    Wants to talk about it some time. Related to May 20, 1939 TLS Ernest Hemingway to Ralph MacA. Ingersoll. 6250-a
  - [Ralph MacA. Ingersoll] to Joseph Losey, 1939 March 28, TL carbon copy, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:47)
    Wired Hemingway thanking him for his letter, but does not have the time to visit him. No reason to continue argument any further. Would rather "talk Ernest [Hemingway] out of letting Glazer do it than I would win a suit from him." We will wait and see what will happen. 6250-a
  - Juanita Jensen to Edward Hotchner, 1949 November 22, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. with envelope. (Box-folder 4:48)
    Checked on Col. Richard Cantwell in Army Register. No officer listed with that name. Hopes Papa and Mary got off all right. Heard he had a digestive disorder. Hopes it was a false rumor. 6250-f
  - [Horace Liveright] to Ernest Hemingway, 1925 December 30, TL copy, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:49)
    Everyone in office read The Torrents of Spring about which Fitzgerald wrote so enthusiastically. Who does he think will buy it? It is such a bitter, vicious caricature of Sherwood Anderson. Too few are interested in intellectual travesty to ensure him sale of 700 or 800 copies. Would be cruel to publish had they wanted to. They may be wrong. Eager to read The Sun Also Rises for publication next fall. Discusses jacket for In Our Time, and says Hemingway wrong to accuse them of exploiting him. He is unknown, and needs blurbs on jacket to attract buyers. It will sell some day, after his first successful novel. Conrad was rejected for ten or fifteen years. 6250-a
  - Joseph Losey to Ralph MacA. Ingersoll, 1939 March 24, TLS, 3 p. on 3 l. (Box-folder 4:50)
    Received copy of Speiser's letter, which makes him mad. Discusses his negotiation with Dart and Speiser regarding script. Ingersoll admits that it "is quite true that a playwright's contract gives him the right to insist upon every word of the script that is bought being produced as bought. However, I know of no successful or unsuccessful production which operates on this basis actually." Hemingway apparently not willing to make any concessions. Raising money for production difficult because, since it was a Hemingway play, people "were worried beforehand about how he would behave in rehearsal, and therefore wanted assurances about that behavior, assurances which normally would be taken for granted. Still, Hemingway would be "a hell of a guy to work with, but I nevertheless liked what I saw of him very much." The play should be produced not only because of Hemingway but because of the cause which it is identified. Enclosed in Joseph Losey to Ralph MacA. Ingersoll, 1939 March 24. Dictated 1939 March 23. 6250-a
  - Joseph Losey to Ralph MacA. Ingersoll, 1939 March 24, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l. with enclosure. (Box-folder 4:51)
    Enclosing a letter which he dictated yesterday. Ingersoll admits that Hemingway behaved well. Although bad judgment on Hemingway's part, best not to antagonize him because "he is fundamentally too useful a guy." Admits original mistake was his own because he was over anxious to do Hemingway's play. 6250-a
  - Dave [?] to Edward Naumburg"> 1950 October 13, TLS, 1950 October 13, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:52)
    Encloses Hemingway reviews for Naumburg. Reviews filed under Various clippings regarding Ernest Hemingway, 1941-1963, n.d. 6250-u
- Series III: Miscellaneous Manuscripts
  - Ernest Hemingway's note regarding Archibald MacLeish, [ca. 1932], AMsS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:53)
    Perhaps intended as a dusk jacket blurb, Hemingway states that anyone interested in reading great poetry as it is published and "before it becomes classic and compulsory" should read Conquistador and New Found Land. 6250-c
  - Envelope signed by Ernest Hemingway to Edward Hotchner, 1950 July [3], D, 1 item. (Box-folder 4:54)
  - Contract, 1950 April 6, DS, 1 p. on 1 l. (Box-folder 4:55)
    Document empowers Edward Hotchner as Hemingway's sole representative for the adaptation of Hemingway's short story, The Capital of the World, into a ballet. Signed by Ernest Hemingway. 6250-f
  - Announcements for Across the River and Into the Trees, [ca. 1950], Ds, 2 items. (Box-folder 4:56)
    6250-u